Guide to the Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Washington Square Book Center (Bookstore), 1938-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Basement Security Camera, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5881; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 52)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5883; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 53)
    - Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5885; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Rodriguez, Robert F. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 54)
    - Cashier, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5887; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 55)
    - Barnes and Noble Bookstore, 5th Avenue at 18th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5889; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 56)
    - Security Camera Monitors, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5891; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 57)
    - Information Desk, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5892; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 58)
    - Entrance Turnstiles, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5895; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 59)
    - Set Your Own Price Book Display, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5897; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 60)
    - Display of George Orwell Works, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5899; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 61)
    - Strand Bookstore, 828 Broadway at 12th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5901; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 62)
    - Entrance, New York University Book Center, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5903; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 63)
    - All Shoplifters Will Be Prosecuted Sign, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5905; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 64)
    - Shoplifter Arrested for Stealing Books, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5907; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 65)
      Crime and criminals; New York University |x Buildings.
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5909; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 66)
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5911; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 67)
    - Security Mirror, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5913; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 68)
    - Shelving Books, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_re5915; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 69)
    - Entrance, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5917; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 70)
    - Merchandise Display, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5919; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 71)
    - Modeling Merchandise, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5921; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 72)
  - Breevort Hotel, circa 1890-1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th 9th Street, circa 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5924; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th Street, circa 1890; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5926; black-and-white print (photograph), 10 x 13 inches (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Exteriors, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5927 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Corner of Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Awning, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5932; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 10 inches; Charry, Jonathan (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Student in Front of Brittany Resident Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5934; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5936; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking North, 55 East 10th Street at Broadway, 1966; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5938; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, 1965; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5940; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking West, Undated; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5944; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Broadway Windows, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5947; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Art.; New York University |x Buildings.
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5949; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Interiors, 1968-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - View of Entrance Security Desk from Inside the Elevator, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 8 inches; Rodriguez, Robert F. (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Burglary Scene, Room 604, Brittany Residence Hall, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5954; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5956; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5958; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5960; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 5)
      Dwellings.; New York University |x Buildings.
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5962; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 6)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5964; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5966; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 8)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5968; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 9)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5969; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 10)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5972; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 11)
    - Student Studying, Room 907, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5974; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Three Students, Brittany Residence Hall, circa 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5976; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 13)
    - Two Students, Brittany Residence Hall, 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5978; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 14)
    - Two Students, Brittany Residence Hall, 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5980; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 15)
    - Students and Beds, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5982; black-and-white print (photograph), 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 16)
    - Students and Beds, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5983; black-and-white print (photograph), 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 17)
    - Fire Sprinkler System, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5986; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 18)
    - Lounge (Villa Marbona), Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5988; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 19)
  - Bronfman Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Drawing of Exterior, Bronfnam Center, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5991; color print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Drawing of Exterior, Bronfman Center, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5993; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Two Students in the Library, Bronfman Center, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5995; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - 715 - 725 Broadway (TSOA Building), 1964-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - View of Building from Washington Pl. and Broadway, Street Level, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6004; Black and White Print, (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - 725 Broadway, Building Facade, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6005; Black and White print (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6011; Black and White print, (photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North, February 1, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6013; Black and White print, (photograph) 8 x 10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - 725 Broadway, Detail of Arch, Columns and Windows, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6015; Black and White print, (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 5)
      Architecture.; Art.; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - 721 Broadway, Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6018; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 6)
      Architecture.; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - 721-725 Broadway, New Tisch School of Arts (TSOA) Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6020; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5 x 8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 7)
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6022; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - 725 Broadway, Building Entrance, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6024; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 9)
    - 719-721 Broadway, Building Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6026; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 10)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, April 16, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6028; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - 725 Broadway, Waverly Place Street View, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6030; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - 721 Broadway, Unauthorized Persons Will Be Subject To Criminal Trespass (sign), undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6032; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications Building, February 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6034; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (vertical), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6036; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 15)
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (horizontal), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6038; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 16)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking West on Washington Place, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6040; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 17)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6042; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 8, Item 18)
  - Brown Building
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene and Washington Place Looking North West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6047; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 1)
      Architecture.; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Real Estate.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - Brown Building, Aerial view of Corner of Greene and Washington Place from Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6049; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side of Greene Street Looking North from Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6051; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side Corner of Greene Street Looking North From Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6053; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - Triangle Fire Plaque on Brown Building, April 27, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6055; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - Brown Building, Ceremony in Council Room with Mr. Frederick Brown, Mrs Frederick Brown, Dr. William H. Nichols, Vice President of the Council, and Chancellor Elmer Ellsworth Brown (left to right), April 22, 1929; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6057; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene Street, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6060; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - Brown Building, seen from Greene Street and Washington Place intersection, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6062; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - View of Washington Pl. from the Brown Building between Greene St. and Washington Square Place, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6064; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - Washington Square North looking down from the Brown Bldg., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6066; Black and White print (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - Frederick Brown Building Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6068; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Brown Building, Washington Square North, Washington Place at Greene Street, March, 26, 1984; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6071; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 12)
    - Henry James Plaque, Brown Building, March 10, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6073; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 2, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - Brown Building - Biology and Chemistry Laboratories, 1969
    - Cell Biology Research Center New York University, Artist's Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6077; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Brown Building Chemistry Lab, Room 553, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6079; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Brown Building Biology Lab, Room 601, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6081; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Carter Hall
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Building Facade, 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6083; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches; Prince, James (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Front Door Molding Detail, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6085; Black and White Print, (Photoraph), 8x10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Computer-Generated Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6089; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 7x5 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6091; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Cantor Film Center Dedication with Norman F. Cantor, Alec Baldwin and Spike Lee., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6093; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 3)
      Baldwin, Alec, 1958-; Cantor, Norman F.; Lee, Spike; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
  - Casa Italiana
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, Watercolor, 1990; UA_PHOTO_001_REF6140; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southeast, Watercolor, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6142; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, Drawing, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6144; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x 5 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6146; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6148; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Casa Italiana, Winfield Scott House National Historic Landmark Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6150; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Up At Windows, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6152; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Casa Italiana, Auditorium, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6154; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Chemistry Building, Artist's Rendering
    - Chemistry Building, Johnson and Foster, Sketch, January 26, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6157; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Clinton Hall, Beekman and Nassau Streets
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, The First Home of the University, Sketch, April 13, 1956; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6160; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, Sketch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6162; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x9 1/4 inches (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Clinton Hall, Sketch, undated; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Catholic Center
      - Catholic Center Site, Thompson Street and Washington Square South, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6095; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Catholic Student Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6101; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Aerial View of Catholic Center, Loeb and Shimkin, Looking East, October 2, 1959; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6103; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Catholic Center, Washington Square South, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6105; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Catholic Center, Stained Glass and Steeple, circa 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6107; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Catholic Center, Soup Kitchen, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6109; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Catholic Center, Demolished For Bobst Library Site, February 1, 1952; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6111; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Catholic Center, Penthouse, November 17, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6113; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Catholic Center, Cross Installation, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6115; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3x5 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Site of Catholic Center, Looking Southeast, January 18, 1961; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6117; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Catholic Center, Drawing, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6119; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 inches; Eggers & Higgins. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Catholic Center, Facade and Plan, Drawing, April 10, 1961; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6121; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Eggers & Higgins. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - Catholic Center, Looking Southeast, Artist's Rendering, 1960; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6123; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Eggers & Higgins. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 13)
        New York University. Washington Square Campus.
      - Dedication of Catholic Center, Archbishop of New York Francis Cardinal Spellman and NYU President Hester, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6125; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 14)
        Hester, James M., 1924-; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
      - Dedication of Catholic Center, Religious Procession In Front of Center, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6127; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 15)
      - Dedication of Catholic Center, Religious Procession Through Streets, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6129; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Seligson, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 16)
      - Dedication of Catholic Center, Archibishop of New York Francis Cardinal Spellman and NYU President Hester, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6131; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 17)
      - Dedication of Catholic Center, Church Ceremony, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6133; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 18)
      - Catholic Center Meeting at Gracie Mansion with Mrs. Wagner and Father O'Reilly, January 22, 1959; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6135; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Gooen, Irwin (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 19)
        Wagner, Lindsay
      - Catholic Center, Church Interior, circa 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_re6137; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 20)
  - Coach Station, Corner of Fourth and Wooster Streets
    - Coach Station at Number 76 Washington Square, South Corner of Fourth and Worcester Streets, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6167; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - D'Agostino Hall Construction